{
    "id": "ed5540dbe1004b03aa54050bf0622ada",
    "title": "Questions Worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9850bee42f43492c98d0067642dd169f",
            "title": "Questions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": ".............................. old is your sister?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "How",
                        "How much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "'................................... is your mother?' 'My mother is a doctor.'",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. does your father work?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Which",
                        "Where"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. is your brotherâ€™s name?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ you like science fiction?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Has",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................. gave you this watch?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who",
                        "Whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. do you spend your holidays?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Where"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... is your favorite writer?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Which",
                        "What",
                        "Who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... you collect stamps?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Have",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. brothers and sisters do you have?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "How many",
                        "How much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}